Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part One
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Files, 1710-1955; 21.07; (65 boxes)
  - Stanhope, Philip Henry Stanhope, Earl, 1805-1875, 1839-43 (Box 56, Folder 2035)
  - Staniland, Charles Joseph, 1838-1916, 1883 (Box 56, Folder 2036)
  - Stanley, Arthur Penrhyn, 1815-1881, 1860-80, undated (Box 56, Folder 2037-2038)
  - Stanley, Augusta, Lady, 1822-1876, 1869-72, undated (Box 56, Folder 2039)
  - Stanley, Dorothy, Lady, d. 1926, undated (Box 56, Folder 2040)
  - Stanley, Edward John Stanley, Baron, 1802-1869, 1861 (Box 56, Folder 2041)
  - Stanley, M., Miss, undated (Box 56, Folder 2042)
  - Stanley-Massey-Stanley, Thomas, Sir, Bart., 1782-1841, 1831 (Box 56, Folder 2043)
  - Stannard, Alfred, 1806-1889 (Box 56, Folder 2044)
  - Stannard, Henrietta Eliza Vaughan Palmer, 1856-1911, 1894-1902 (Box 56, Folder 2045)
  - Stebbing, Henry, 1799-1883, 1878 (Box 56, Folder 2046)
  - Steer, Fanny, fl. 1846-1860, 1859 (Box 56, Folder 2047)
  - Stephanoff, Francis Philip, 1788-1860, 1840, undated (Box 56, Folder 2048)
  - Stephanoff, James, 1788?-1874, 1820-64, undated (Box 56, Folder 2049)
  - Stephen, James Fitzjames, Sir, 1829- 1894, 1854-79, undated (Box 56, Folder 2050)
  - Stephens, George, 1813-1895, 1869 (Box 56, Folder 2051)
  - Stevenson, Robert Alan Mowbray, 1847- 1900, 1897 (Box 56, Folder 2052)
  - Stirling, Arthur, 1889 (Box 56, Folder 2053)
  - Stirling, Edward, 1807-1894, 1886, undated (Box 56, Folder 2054)
  - Stirling, Fanny, 1815-1895, undated (Box 56, Folder 2055)
  - Stockmar, Christian Friedrich, Baron von, 1787-1863, 1831-42, undated (Box 56, Folder 2056)
  - Stocks, Arthur, 1846-1889, 1867, undated (Box 56, Folder 2057)
  - Stocks, Lumb, 1812-1892, 1856, undated (Box 56, Folder 2058)
  - Stokes, Adrian, 1854-1935, 1894 (Box 56, Folder 2059)
  - Stone, Marcus, 1840-1921, 1882-98 (Box 56, Folder 2060)
  - Stopford, Horatia Charlotte Frances, Hon., 1835-1920, 1875-76 (Box 57, Folder 2061)
  - Storey, George Adolphus, 1834-1919, 1876-99, undated (Box 57, Folder 2062)
  - Stothard, Alfred Joseph, 1793-1864, 1840 (Box 57, Folder 2063)
  - Stothard, Thomas, 1755-1834, 1815-31, undated (Box 57, Folder 2064)
  - Stoughton, John, 1807-1897, undated (Box 57, Folder 2065)
  - Stachey, Jane Maria Grant, Lady, 1840- 1928, 1899, undated (Box 57, Folder 2066)
  - Stradbroke, John Edward Cornwallis, Earl of, 1794-1886, 1841-60 (Box 57, Folder 2067)
  - Strafford, George Henry Charles Byng, Earl of, 1830-1898, 1861-95 (Box 57, Folder 2068)
  - Strafford, George Stevens Byng, Earl of, 1806-1886, 1835-65, undated (Box 57, Folder 2069)
  - Strangford, Emily Anne Beauford Smythe, Viscountess, 1826-1887, 1877-82, undated (Box 57, Folder 2070)
  - Strangford, Percy Clinton Sydney Smythe, Viscount, 1780-1855, 1853 (Box 57, Folder 2071)
  - Strangford, Percy Ellen Frederick William Smythe, Viscount, 1826-1869, 1852-68, undated (Box 57, Folder 2072)
  - Stratford de Redcliffe, Eliza Charlotte (Alexander) Canning, d. 1882, 1857 (Box 57, Folder 2073)
  - Stratford de Redcliffe, Stratford Canning, Viscount, 1786-1880, 1862-68, undated (Box 57, Folder 2074)
  - Strutt, Jacob George, 1790-1864, 1897 (Box 57, Folder 2075)
  - Stuart, Charles, fl. 1854-1893, 1888 (Box 57, Folder 2076)
  - Stuart-Wortley, James Archibald, 1805- 1881, 1850, undated (Box 57, Folder 2077)
  - Studholme, Marie, b. 1875, 1891-1901, undated (Box 57, Folder 2078)
  - Sudway, Robert Charles, 1842 (Box 57, Folder 2079)
  - Sugden, Charles, 1850-1921, undated (Box 57, Folder 2080)
  - Sugden, Edward Burtenshaw, 1781-1875, 1807-67, undated (Box 57, Folder 2081)
  - Sumner, Charles, 1790-1874, 1828-65, undated (Box 57, Folder 2082)
  - Surrey Theatre, undated (Box 57, Folder 2083)
  - Sutherland, Harriet Elizabeth Georgiana (Howard), Sutherland- Leveson-Gower, Duchess of, 1806-1868, undated (Box 57, Folder 2084)
  - Sutter, Julia, 1888 (Box 57, Folder 2085)
  - Swanwick, Anna, 1813-1899, 1880, undated (Box 57, Folder 2086)
  - Swarbreck, Samuel Dukinfield, fl. 1839-1863, 1855 (Box 57, Folder 2087)
  - Swinstead, Charles Hillyard, fl. 1863- 1891, 1887 (Box 57, Folder 2088)
  - Sydenham, Charles Edward Poulett Thomson, Baron, 1799-1841, undated (Box 57, Folder 2089)
  - Sydney, John Robert Townshend, Earl, 1805-1890, 1831-51, undated (Box 57, Folder 2090)
  - Symons, William Robert, fl. 1876-1893, 1885 (Box 57, Folder 2091)
  - Tahourdin, Richard, b. 1847, 1904 (Box 57, Folder 2092)
  - Talbot, John Gilbert, 1835-1910, 1870-87 (Box 57, Folder 2093)
  - Talbot de Malahide, James Talbot, Baron, 1805-1883, 1864 (Box 57, Folder 2094)
  - Tankerville, Charles Augustus Bennet, Earl of, 1810-1899, 1860-72 (Box 57, Folder 2095)
  - Tarver, C., undated (Box 57, Folder 2096)
  - Tate, Henry, 1872-1940, undated (Box 57, Folder 2097)
  - Tayler, Frederick, 1802-1889, 1850-83, undated (Box 58, Folder 2098)
  - Tayler, Leo, undated (Box 58, Folder 2099)
  - Taylor, Alfred Swaine, 1806-1880, undated (Box 58, Folder 2100)
  - Taylor, Bayard, 1825-1878, undated (Box 58, Folder 2101)
  - Taylor, Herbert, Sir, 1775-1839, 1827-42 (Box 58, Folder 2102)
  - Taylor, Isaac, 1829-1901, 1894 (Box 58, Folder 2103)
  - Taylor, John Ellor, 1837-1895, 1880 (Box 58, Folder 2104)
  - Taylor, Norman, fl. 1863-1893, 1890 (Box 58, Folder 2105)
  - Taylor, Tom, 1817-1880, 1859 (Box 58, Folder 2106)
  - Taylor, Wilbraham, 1847 (Box 58, Folder 2107)
  - Tearle, George Osmond, 1852-1901, 1890 (Box 58, Folder 2108)
  - Teck, Prince Francis Paul Louis Alexander, Duke of, 1830?-1900, 1875-95, undated (Box 58, Folder 2109)
  - Teck, Princess Mary Adelaide, Duchess of, 1833-1897, 1869-95, undated (Box 58, Folder 2110)
  - Teesdale, Christopher Charles, Sir, 1833-1893, undated (Box 58, Folder 2111)
  - Teignmouth, Charles John Shore, Baron, 1796-1885, 1845-79, undated (Box 58, Folder 2112)
  - Temple, Richard, b. 1847, undated (Box 58, Folder 2113)
  - Temple, William, 1847 (Box 58, Folder 2114)
  - Tennent, James Emerson, Sir, 1804-1869, 1833-67, undated (Box 58, Folder 2115)
  - Terriss, Ellaline, 1872-1971, 1901 (Box 58, Folder 2116)
  - Terriss, William, 1847-1897, 1887-94, undated (Box 58, Folder 2117)
  - Terry, Charles, 1857-1933, 1902 (Box 58, Folder 2118)
  - Terry, Dame Ellen, 1848-1928, 1878-92, undated (Box 58, Folder 2119)
  - Terry, Edward O'Connor, 1844-1912, 1892-1910, undated (Box 58, Folder 2120)
  - Terry, Fred, 1863-1933, 1894-1905, undated (Box 58, Folder 2121)
  - Terry, Kate, 1844-1924, 1866-1903, undated (Box 58, Folder 2122)
  - Terry, Mabel, b. 1872, undated (Box 58, Folder 2123)
  - Terry, Marion, 1856-1930, 1886-1906, undated (Box 58, Folder 2124)
  - Teynham, George Henry Roper-Curzon, Baron, 1798-1889, 1866, undated (Box 58, Folder 2125)
  - Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1811- 1863, undated (Box 58, Folder 2126)
  - Thistleton-Dyer, William Turner, Sir, 1843-1928, 1914 (Box 58, Folder 2127)
  - Thomas, Brandon, 1856-1914, 1872-85, undated (Box 58, Folder 2128)
  - Thomas, George Houseman, 1824-1868, 1863 (Box 58, Folder 2129)
  - Thomas, W. Cave, fl. 1843-84, undated (Box 58, Folder 2130)
  - Thomas, William Luson, 1830-1900, 1893 (Box 58, Folder 2131)
  - Thompson, Alfred, fl. 1863-1876, undated (Box 58, Folder 2132)
  - Thompson, Gordon, 1899 (Box 58, Folder 2133)
  - Thompson, Lydia, 1836-1908, undated (Box 58, Folder 2134)
  - Thompson, W. H. (William Hepworth), 1810-1886, undated (Box 58, Folder 2135)
  - Thomson, Leslie, 1851-1929, 1903, undated (Box 59, Folder 2136)
  - Thomson, William, 1819-1890, 1861-89 (Box 59, Folder 2137)
  - Thornbury, Walter, 1828-1876, undated (Box 59, Folder 2138)
  - Thorne, Emily, 1882 (Box 59, Folder 2139)
  - Thorne, Frederick, 1882-86 (Box 59, Folder 2140)
  - Thorne, George, 1888-92 (Box 59, Folder 2141)
  - Thorne, Thomas, 1841-1918, 1877-90, undated (Box 59, Folder 2142)
  - Thornton, Richard, 1777-1862 (Box 59, Folder 2143)
  - Thornycroft, William Hamo, Sir, 1850- 1925, 1881-97, undated (Box 59, Folder 2144)
  - Thorpe, Markham John, 1845 (Box 59, Folder 2145)
  - Thurlow, Thomas John Hovell-Thurlow- Cumming-Bruce, Baron, 1838-1916, 1889 (Box 59, Folder 2146)
  - Thynne, Charles, Lord, 1813-1894, 1857-77 (Box 59, Folder 2147)
  - Thynne, John, Lord, 1798-1881, 1853 (Box 59, Folder 2148)
  - Ticknor, T. B., 1871 (Box 59, Folder 2149)
  - Tindal, Nicholas Conyngham, Sir, 1776- 1846, 1834-45, undated (Box 59, Folder 2150)
  - Tinworth, George, 1843-1913, 1888, undated (Box 59, Folder 2151)
  - Titchfield, William Henry Cavendish Cavendish-Scott-Bentinck, Marquis of, 1796-1824, 1822 (Box 59, Folder 2152)
  - Todd, James Henthorn, 1805-1869, 1844-65 (Box 59, Folder 2153)
  - Tollemache, John Tollemache, Baron, 1805-1890, 1876-82, undated (Box 59, Folder 2154)
  - Tollemache, W. A., 1894 (Box 59, Folder 2155)
  - Tollemache, Wilbraham Frederic Tollemache, Baron, 1832-1904, 1886 (Box 59, Folder 2156)
  - Tomkins, Frederick, 1863 (Box 59, Folder 2157)
  - Tomlinson, J., fl. 1824-1853, 1884 (Box 59, Folder 2158)
  - Tonna, Charlotte Elizabeth, 1790-1846, undated (Box 59, Folder 2159)
  - Tonning (ship), 1854 (Box 59, Folder 2160)
  - Took, William, fl. 1857-1892, undated (Box 59, Folder 2161)
  - Toole, John Lawrence, 1830-1906, 1865-93, undated (Box 59, Folder 2162)
  - Topham, Frank W. W., 1838-1924, 1877, undated (Box 59, Folder 2163)
  - Torrington, George Byng, Viscount, 1812-1884, 1835-63, undated (Box 59, Folder 2164)
  - Townshend, Frederick Henry, 1868-1920, 1911, undated (Box 59, Folder 2165)
  - Townshend, Henry James, fl. 1839-1866, undated (Box 59, Folder 2166)
  - Tree, Herbert Beerbohm, Sir, 1853-1917, 1893-1913, undated (Box 59, Folder 2167)
  - Tree, Maud (Holt), Lady, 1864-1937, undated (Box 59, Folder 2168)
  - Trelawney, William Lewis Salusbury, Sir, Bart., 1781-1856, undated (Box 59, Folder 2169)
  - Trevelyan, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1807-1886, 1872-81 (Box 59, Folder 2170)
  - Troughton, Richard Zouch Serbon, d. 1889, 1888 (Box 60, Folder 2171)
  - Truro, Thomas Wilde, Baron, 1782-1855, 1837-52, undated (Box 60, Folder 2172)
  - Tupper, Martin Farquhar, 1810-1889, 1865-70 (Box 60, Folder 2173)
  - Turner, George, 1798-1883 (Box 60, Folder 2174)
  - Turnerelli, Edward Tracy, 1813-1896, 1885 (Box 60, Folder 2175)
  - Tweedie, Ethel Alec, d. 1940, 1894-1902 (Box 60, Folder 2176)
  - Twiss, Horace, 1787-1849, 1833-41 (Box 60, Folder 2177)
  - Tylor, Edward Burnett, Sir, 1832-1917, 1884-91 (Box 60, Folder 2178)
  - Unidentified, 1860 (Box 60, Folder 2179)
  - Upcott, Willia, 1779-1845, 1841-45 (Box 60, Folder 2180)
  - Uwins, Thomas, 1782-1857, 1840-53, undated (Box 60, Folder 2181)
  - Valentia, Arthur Annesley, Viscount, 1843-1927, 1885-99 (Box 60, Folder 2182)
  - Valentine, Sydney, b.1865, 1899 (Box 60, Folder 2183)
  - Van Brenne, Auguste, 1845-1913, 1887 (Box 60, Folder 2184)
  - Vanbrugh, Irene, Dame, 1872-1949, 1909 (Box 60, Folder 2185)
  - Vanbrugh, Violet, 1867-1942, 1904, undated (Box 60, Folder 2186-2187)
  - Vandenhoff, John, 1790-1861, 1845, undated (Box 60, Folder 2188)
  - Vaughan, Kate, 1852?-1903, 1882, undated (Box 60, Folder 2189)
  - Venn, Lottie, 1852-1928, undated (Box 60, Folder 2190)
  - Verinder, Frederick, 1891 (Box 60, Folder 2191)
  - Verney, Harry, Sir, 1801-1894, 1837-92 (Box 60, Folder 2192)
  - Vernon, Robert, 1774-1849, 1829, undated (Box 60, Folder 2193)
  - Verulam, James Walter Grimston, Earl of, 1852-1924, 1870-80, undated (Box 60, Folder 2194)
  - Verulam, James Walter Grimston, Earl of, 1852-1924, 1886-93, undated (Box 60, Folder 2195)
  - Vezin, Hermann, 1829-1910, 1877-86, undated (Box 60, Folder 2196)
  - Victor, Mary Anne, undated (Box 60, Folder 2197)
  - Victoria, Queen of Great Britain, 1819-1901, 1828-99, undated (Box 60, Folder 2198-2200)
  - Victoria, Consort of Prince Louis of Battenburg, 1863-1950
    See: Milford Haven, Victoria Alberta Elizabeth Mathilde Marie, Marchioness of, 1863-1950, box 42, folder 1482
  - Victoria, Empress, Consort of Frederick III, German Emperor, 1840- 1901, 1862 (Box 60, Folder 2201)
  - Victoria Alexandra Olga Mary, Princess of Great Britain, 1868-1935, 1909-13, undated (Box 60, Folder 2202)
  - Victoria Mary Louisa, Duchess of Kent, 1786-1861, 1837-40, undated (Box 60, Folder 2203)
  - Villiers, Charles Pelham, 1802-1898, 1860, undated (Box 61, Folder 2204)
  - Villiers, Frederic, 1851-1922, undated (Box 61, Folder 2205)
  - Vining, George J., 1824-1875, 1865, undated (Box 61, Folder 2206)
  - Virtue, James Sprent, 1829-1892, undated (Box 61, Folder 2207)
  - Vizetelly, Frank, 1830-1883?, 1870 (Box 61, Folder 2208)
  - Waddington, Horatio, 1799-1867, 1865 (Box 61, Folder 2209)
  - Waddy, Frederick H., 1872 (Box 61, Folder 2210)
  - Wade, John, 1788-1875, undated (Box 61, Folder 2211)
  - Waite, Robert Thorne, 1842-1935, 1890-99, undated (Box 61, Folder 2212)
  - Waldegrave, Mary Dorothea (Palmer) Waldegrave, Lady, d.1933, 1906 (Box 61, Folder 2213)
  - Waldegrave, William Frederick, styled Viscount Chewton, 1816-1854, 1850 (Box 61, Folder 2214)
  - Waldegrave, William Frederick Waldegrave, Earl, 1851-1930, 1884-1908, undated (Box 61, Folder 2215)
  - Walkley, Arthur Bingham, 1855-1926, 1899 (Box 61, Folder 2216)
  - Waller, Lewis, 1860-1915, undated (Box 61, Folder 2217)
  - Waller, Mary Lemon (Fowler), undated (Box 61, Folder 2218)
  - Wallett, William Frederick, undated (Box 61, Folder 2219)
  - Wallis, Ellen Lancaster, b. 1856, 1873, undated (Box 61, Folder 2220)
  - Wallis, Henry, 1804-1890, 1875 (Box 61, Folder 2221)
  - Walpole, Robert, Earl of Oxford, 1676- 1745, 1710-21 (Box 61, Folder 2222)
  - Walpole, Spencer, Sir, 1839-1907, 1891 (Box 61, Folder 2223)
  - Walpole, Spencer H. (Spencer Horatio), 1806-1898, 1873-93, undated (Box 61, Folder 2224)
  - Walsingham, Thomas de Grey, Baron, 1804-1870, 1862-64, undated (Box 61, Folder 2225)
  - Walsingham, Thomas de Grey, Baron, 1843-1919, 1874-1906, undated (Box 61, Folder 2226)
  - Warburton, Henry, 1784?-1858, 1847 (Box 61, Folder 2227)
  - Ward, Ada, 1879, undated (Box 61, Folder 2228)
  - Ward, Alfred, fl. 1873-1893, undated (Box 61, Folder 2229)
  - Ward, Edward Matthew, 1816-1879, 1869-70, undated (Box 61, Folder 2230)
  - Ward, Genevieve, 1838-1922, 1883-1901 (Box 61, Folder 2231)
  - Ward, Henriette Mary Ada Ward, "Mrs. E. M. Ward,", 1832-1924, 1865, undated (Box 61, Folder 2232)
  - Ward, Herbert, 1863-1919, 1894-97 (Box 61, Folder 2233)
  - Ward, Leslie, Sir, 1851-1922, 1892-1902 (Box 61, Folder 2234)
  - Ward, William, fl. 1860-1876, 1864-71 (Box 61, Folder 2235)
  - Waring, Herbert, b. 1857, undated (Box 61, Folder 2236)
  - Warner, Charles, 1846-1909, 1880-1909, undated (Box 61, Folder 2237)
  - Warner, Mary Amelia (Huddart), 1804- 1854, undated (Box 61, Folder 2238)
  - Warren, Edmund George, fl. 1852-1893, 1869 (Box 61, Folder 2239)
  - Warren, Henry, 1794-1879, undated (Box 61, Folder 2240)
  - Warwick, Frances Evelyn Maynard Greville, Countess of, 1861-1933, undated (Box 61, Folder 2241)
  - Warwick, Francis Richard Charles Guy Greville, Earl of, 1853-1924, 1892-96 (Box 61, Folder 2242)
  - Warwick, George Guy Greville, Earl of, 1818-1893, 1861-83, undated (Box 61, Folder 2243)
  - Waterhouse, Alfred, 1830-1905, 1876-88 (Box 61, Folder 2244)
  - Waterhouse, G.R. (George Robert), 1810-1888, 1833 (Box 61, Folder 2245)
  - Waterhouse, John William, 1849-1917, undated (Box 61, Folder 2246)
  - Waterlow, Ernest Albert, Sir, 1850- 1919, 1890 (Box 61, Folder 2247)
  - Watson, Richard, 1737-1816, 1798-1805 (Box 61, Folder 2248)
  - Watson, Thomas Henry, b. 1839, 1851-61 (Box 61, Folder 2249)
  - Watts, J. Hunter, 1897 (Box 61, Folder 2250)
  - Webb, Charles, 1867, undated (Box 62, Folder 2251)
  - Webb, Keet, 1870 (Box 62, Folder 2252)
  - Webb, T. W. (Thomas William), 1807-1885, 1862 (Box 62, Folder 2253)
  - Webster, Benjamin, 1797-1882, 1830-82, undated (Box 62, Folder 2254)
  - Webster, Benjamin, 1864-1947, 1899-1901 (Box 62, Folder 2255)
  - Webster, Frederick, 1852 (Box 62, Folder 2256)
  - Webster, Thomas, 1800-1886, 1845, undated (Box 62, Folder 2257)
  - Weir, Emma Frances, 1856 (Box 62, Folder 2258)
  - Welch, James, 1865-1917, 1896-1907, undated (Box 62, Folder 2259)
  - Wellesley, Gerald Valerian, 1809-1882, 1865-73, undated (Box 62, Folder 2260)
  - Wellesley, Mrs., undated (Box 62, Folder 2261)
  - Wellington, Arthur Richard Wellesley, Duke of, 1807-1884, 1833-86, undated (Box 62, Folder 2262)
  - Wellington, Arthur Wellesley, Duke of, 1769-1852, 1835, undated (Box 62, Folder 2263)
  - Wellington, Elizabeth (Hay) Wellesley, Duchess of, 1820-1904, 1901, undated (Box 62, Folder 2264)
  - Wells, Henry Tanforth, 1828-1903, 1886-94, undated (Box 62, Folder 2265)
  - Wells, Spencer, 1818-1897, 1883-93, undated (Box 62, Folder 2266)
  - Wemall (?), John A., 1909 (Box 62, Folder 2267)
  - Wemyss, Francis Charteris-Wemyss- Douglas, Earl of, 1772-1853, 1849 (Box 62, Folder 2268)
  - Wemyss, Francis Wemyss Charteris Douglas, Earl of, 1818-1914, 1860-99, undated (Box 62, Folder 2269)
  - Wenlock, Beilby Lawley, Baron, 1849- 1912, 1860-90, undated (Box 62, Folder 2270)
  - Wensleydale, James Parke, Baron, 1782- 1868, 1830-65, undated (Box 62, Folder 2271)
  - West, Joseph Walter, d. 1933, 1901, undated (Box 62, Folder 2272)
  - Westbury, Richard Bethell, Baron, 1800-1873, 1838-63, undated (Box 62, Folder 2273)
  - Westcott, W. Wynn (William Wynn), 1848-1925, 1908 (Box 62, Folder 2274)
  - Western, C. C. (Charles Callis), Baron Western, 1767-1844, 1837-43, undated (Box 62, Folder 2275)
  - Westerton, Frank H., 1897 (Box 62, Folder 2276)
  - Westminster, Constance Gertrude (Leveson-Gower) Grosvenor, Duchess of, d. 1880, undated (Box 62, Folder 2277)
  - Westminster, Hugh Lupus Grosvenor, Duke of, 1825-1899, 1840-93, undated (Box 62, Folder 2278)
  - Westminster, Richard Grosvenor, Marquis of, 1795-1869, 1847-65 (Box 62, Folder 2279)
  - Westminster, Robert Grosvenor, Marquis of, 1767-1845, 1840-50, undated (Box 62, Folder 2280)
  - Westwood, J. O. (John Obadiah), 1805- 1893, 1864 (Box 62, Folder 2281)
  - Whalley, G. H. (George Hammond), 1813- 1878, 1870-71, undated (Box 62, Folder 2282)
  - Wharncliffe, Edward Montagu Stuart Granville Stuart-Wortley-Mackenzie, Earl of, 1827-1899, 1852-90 (Box 62, Folder 2283)
  - Wheatley, Henry, Sir, fl. 1834, 1835-40 (Box 62, Folder 2284)
  - Whewell, William, 1794-1866, 1860 (Box 62, Folder 2285)
  - Whistler, James McNeill, 1834-1903, 1886-99, undated (Box 63, Folder 2286)
  - White, Henry Julian, 1859-1934, undated (Box 63, Folder 2287)
  - White, John, fl. 1877-1893, 1888 (Box 63, Folder 2288)
  - White, William Arthur, Sir, 1824-1891, 1889, undated (Box 63, Folder 2289)
  - Whitehouse, Cope, 1888 (Box 63, Folder 2290)
  - Whitelaw, Fanny (Horsley), Lady, 1899 (Box 63, Folder 2291)
  - Whiteley, William, 1831-1907, 1895 (Box 63, Folder 2292)
  - Wickham, Agnes (Gladstone), 1842-1931, undated (Box 63, Folder 2293)
  - Wigan, Alfred, 1814-1878, 1864-72, undated (Box 63, Folder 2294)
  - Wigan, Horace, 1818?-1885, 1852-73, undated (Box 63, Folder 2295)
  - Wigan, Lenora (Pincott), 1805-1884, undated (Box 63, Folder 2296)
  - Wilberforce, William, 1759-1833, undated (Box 63, Folder 2297)
  - Wilde, W. J., 1864 (Box 63, Folder 2298)
  - Wilkie, David, Sir, 1785-1841, 1818 (Box 63, Folder 2299)
  - Wilkie, Henry C., 1894 (Box 63, Folder 2300)
  - Willard, E. S., 1853-1915, 1889-1905, undated (Box 63, Folder 2301)
  - William IV, King of Great Britain, 1765-1837, undated (Box 63, Folder 2302)
  - William Frederick, Duke of Gloucester, 1776-1834, 1813, undated (Box 63, Folder 2303)
  - Williams, Alfred, 1832-1905, undated (Box 63, Folder 2304)
  - Williams, Arthur, b. 1844, 1895-97 (Box 63, Folder 2305)
  - Williams, Barney, 1824-1876, undated (Box 63, Folder 2306)
  - Williams, Charles, 1838-1904, 1901 (Box 63, Folder 2307)
  - Williams, George, 1814-1878, 1850 (Box 63, Folder 2308)
  - Williams, John Carvell, 1821-1907, 1886-93, undated (Box 63, Folder 2309)
  - Williams, Penry, 1800?-1885, undated (Box 63, Folder 2310)
  - Williams, Thomas L., 1867 (Box 63, Folder 2311)
  - Willis, Henry Brittan, 1810-1884, undated (Box 63, Folder 2312)
  - Willis, Nathaniel Parker, 1806-1867, undated (Box 63, Folder 2313)
  - Willmott, J., undated (Box 63, Folder 2314)
  - Willott, William, 1859 (Box 63, Folder 2315)
  - Willoughby de Eresby, Alberic Drummond-Willoughby, Baron, 1821-1870, undated (Box 63, Folder 2316)
  - Willoughby de Eresby, Peter Robert Drummond Burrell, Baron, 1782-1865, 1823-45 (Box 63, Folder 2317-2318)
  - Wilson, Charles Rivers, Sir, 1831-1916, 1869-93 (Box 63, Folder 2319)
  - Wilson, Dower, 1878 (Box 63, Folder 2320)
  - Wilson, Oscar, 1867-1930, undated (Box 63, Folder 2321)
  - Wilson, Sarah Isabella Augusta (Spencer-Churchill), Lady, 1875-1929, undated (Box 63, Folder 2322)
  - Wilson, Thomas Walter, b. 1851, 1886-95, undated (Box 63, Folder 2323)
  - Wimperis, Edmund Morison, 1835-1900, 1899 (Box 63, Folder 2324)
  - Wingfield, Lewis, 1842-1891, undated (Box 63, Folder 2325)
  - Winter, John Strange, 1856-1911
    See: Stannard, Henrietta Eliza Vaughan Palmer, 1856-1911, box 56, folder 2045
  - Winterhalter, Franz Xavier, 1805-1873, undated (Box 63, Folder 2326)
  - Wivell, Abraham, 1786-1849, undated (Box 64, Folder 2327)
  - Wolff, Georgiana Mary (Walpole), Lady, d. 1859, 1851 (Box 64, Folder 2328)
  - Wolff, Henry Drummond, Sir, 1830-1908, 1859-90 (Box 64, Folder 2329)
  - Wolff, Joseph, 1795-1862, 1826-61, undated (Box 64, Folder 2330)
  - Wolseley, Garnet Wolseley, Viscount, 1833-1913, 1887 (Box 64, Folder 2331)
  - Wood, Arthur Augustus, 1824-1907, 1880, undated (Box 64, Folder 2332)
  - Wood, Henry Trueman, 1845-1929, 1892 (Box 64, Folder 2333)
  - Wood, James, 1760-1839, 1834 (Box 64, Folder 2334)
  - Wood, J. G. (John George), 1827-1889, 1886 (Box 64, Folder 2335)
  - Wood, Matilda Charlotte, 1833-1915, undated (Box 64, Folder 2336)
  - Wood, Theodore, 1862-1923, 1909 (Box 64, Folder 2337)
  - Woodington, William Frederick, 1806- 1893, undated (Box 64, Folder 2338)
  - Woods, Albert William, Sir, 1816-1904, 1831-80, undated (Box 64, Folder 2339)
  - Woods, Henry George, 1842-1915, 1896 (Box 64, Folder 2340)
  - Woodward, Alice B., fl. 1886-1892, 1901 (Box 64, Folder 2341)
  - Woodward, B. B. (Bernard Bolingbroke), 1816-1869, undated (Box 64, Folder 2342)
  - Woolgar, Sarah Jane, 1824-1909, 1884, undated (Box 64, Folder 2343)
  - Wornum, Ralph Nicholson, 1812-1877, 1869 (Box 64, Folder 2344)
  - Worsley-Holmes, Anne Redstone (Delgarno), Lady, 1793-1857, 1841 (Box 64, Folder 2345)
  - Wrench, Benjamin, 1778-1843, 1835 (Box 64, Folder 2346)
  - Wright, Edward Richard, 1813-1859, undated (Box 64, Folder 2347)
  - Wright, Fred, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 2348)
  - Wright, John, d. 1881, 1864 (Box 64, Folder 2349)
  - Wright, Joseph, 1855-1930, 1895 (Box 64, Folder 2350)
  - Wright, William Aldis, 1831-1914, 1873 (Box 64, Folder 2351)
  - Wriglesworth, John, 1842 (Box 64, Folder 2352)
  - Wrottesley, Arthur Wrottesley, Baron, 1824-1910, 1870-73 (Box 64, Folder 2353)
  - Wyatt, M. Digby (Matthew Digby), Sir, 1820-1877, 1871 (Box 64, Folder 2354)
  - Wyllie, Charles W., 1859-1923, 1901 (Box 64, Folder 2355)
  - Wyllie, W. L. (William Lionel), 1851- 1931, 1898 (Box 64, Folder 2356)
  - Wyndham, Charles, Sir, 1837-1919, 1891, undated (Box 64, Folder 2357)
  - Wyndham, Mary (Moore) Albany, 1861- 1931, 1899-1909 (Box 64, Folder 2358)
  - Wynfield, David Wilkie, 1837-1887, undated (Box 64, Folder 2359)
  - Wynne, Edith, 1870-73 (Box 64, Folder 2360)
  - Wyon, Joseph Shepherd, 1836-1873, 1856-60 (Box 65, Folder 2361)
  - Yarrell, William, 1784-1856, undated (Box 65, Folder 2362)
  - Yates, Edmund Hodgson, 1831-1894, 1871-88, undated (Box 65, Folder 2363-2364)
  - Yeames, William Frederick, 1835-1918, 1868-99, undated (Box 65, Folder 2365)
  - Yonge, Charles Duke, 1812-1891, 1866 (Box 65, Folder 2366)
  - Yonge, Charlotte Mary, 1823-1901, undated (Box 65, Folder 2367)